I'm
typing out the coordinates on the terminal
screen
The cleanest set of numbers that I've ever seen I
know you're out there burning in the asteroid
field
I know you're pushing hard against the broken
shield.
But I'm standing in the center of the quiet and
the clear.
I'm sending out a signal just to let you know I'm
here.
The radar is sweeping, the sequence is locked.
The data is streaming, the channel is docked.
Across the dark vacuum, across the great
divide, a burst of information from the other
side. Telemetry! Pinching in the dots Shooting
out a message like a digital spark Telemetry
Reading out the lines Looking at the numbers and
decoding the signs I won't let you pull me I won't
let you drag me down But I'll send you the
telemetry from my side of town
I can see a friction burning up the atmosphere.
You're running on the edge, you're running on
the gear.
But I am in the Goldilocks, the temperature is
right.
I'm just a glowing beacon in the middle of your
night.
Data, read the math, adjust your heavy spin
But I am keeping the perimeter, you cannot enter
in
The radar is sweeping, the sequence is locked.
The data is streaming, the channel is docked.
Across the dark vacuum, across the great
divide, a burst of information from the other
side. Telemetry, pinging in the dark, shooting
out a message like a digital spark. Telemetry,
Reading up the lines, looking at the numbers and
decoding the signs I won't let you pull me, I
won't let you drag me down
But I'll send you the telemetry from my side of
town
Signal out. Signal received. The distance is
maintained. The sanctuary.
The chief. Telemetry, pinging in the dark
Shooting out a message like a digital spark
Telemetry, reading up the lines Looking at the
numbers and decoding the signs I won't let you
pull me, I won't let you drag me down But I'll send
you the telemetry from my side of town
Signal out. End transmission.
Telemetry free.